bids4cheap.com 2011-10-07

# Privacy | bids4cheap

**PRIVACY POLICY**

**Scope**  
Bids4cheap.com (hereinafter referred to as “Bids4cheap”) is a service provided by Bids4cheap, Inc. (hereinafter referred to as “Bids4cheap” or “We”). We recognize and respect your personal privacy. This Privacy Policy describes all aspects relating to gathering information while you are visiting the Bids4cheap website, how We handle your personal information for our services and all further permissible uses of such information.

By accepting the Privacy Policy and the Terms and Conditions in registration, you expressly consent to our collection, storage, use and disclosure of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective upon acceptance for new users and is otherwise effective 10 days after being posted on the website.

**Data Collection**  
You may visit Bids4cheap at any time without providing your identity or revealing any personal information about yourself. However, when you visit our website, we may collect and store your computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and from Bids4cheap, ad data, IP address and standard web log information and information from other companies, such as demographic and navigation data.  
For you to actively participate in Bids4cheap we do need some of your personal information, however. Once you provide us with your required personal information, you are no longer anonymous. In providing us with your personal information, you consent to the transfer and storage of such information on our servers.  
In connection with your registration and use of Bids4cheap We may collect and store the following personal information:

  * email address and physical contact information including but not limited to your name, address, date of birth and telephone number; 
  * all transactional information based on your activities on Bids4cheap; 
  * shipping, billing and other information relating to any purchase or shipping; 
  * any correspondence sent to us; 
  * financial information, such as your credit card information; and 
  * other supplemental information from third parties. 

**Use of Data**  
Our primary purpose in collecting personal information is to provide you with a safe, smooth, efficient, and customized experience. You agree that we may use your personal information to:

  * provide the services and customer support you request; 
  * resolve disputes, collect fees, and troubleshoot problems; 
  * prevent potentially prohibited or illegal activities, and enforce our Terms and Conditions; 
  * customize, measure and improve our services, content and advertising; 
  * inform you about our services, targeted marketing, service updates, and promotional offers; and 
  * compare information for accuracy, and verify it with third parties. 

**Disclosure of Personal Data**  
We may disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our policies, respond to claims that a listing or other content violates the rights of others, or protect anyone\'s rights, property, or safety. Such information will be disclosed in accordance with applicable laws and regulations.  
We may also share your personal information with third parties assisting our business operations under contract, including but not limited to fraud investigations and debt collection, with law enforcement or other governmental officials if required by law, and with other business entities, should we plan to merge with or be acquired by that business entity.  
Without limiting the above, in an effort to respect your privacy and our ability to keep the community free from bad actors, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement, other government officials, or other third parties without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, except when we believe in good faith that the disclosure of information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss or to report suspected illegal activity.

**Providing Data within the Corporate Group**  
We are a member of the Bids4cheap, Inc. . You are consenting to allow your data to be provided within this corporate group. We assure you that should data be provided this way, security and confidentiality will be guaranteed with no change, and that the data will continue to be subject to the Data Protection Statement above.

**Your Information on Bids4cheap**  
Once you have been approved as registered user with Bids4cheap, you will be required to choose a user name. This user name will be displayed throughout Bids4cheap and therefore provided to the public. Unless you associate your user name with your personal information, users will not be able to personally identify your activities on Bids4cheap.  
When visiting Bids4cheap from a public or shared computer, certain information about you, such as your user name, may also be visible to others who may use such the computer after your use.

**Access, Review and Change of Personal Data**  
You can access, review and change most of your personal information by logging on to Bids4cheap at any time. However, some of your personal information can only be changed by contacting our Customer Service. You are required to promptly update your personal information if changes occur or information is inaccurate.

**Revoking Consent/Deleting Your Account**  
Upon your request, we will close your account and remove your personal information from view as soon as reasonably possible, based on your account activity and in accordance with applicable law. We do retain personal information from closed accounts to comply with law, prevent fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our General Terms and Conditions, and take other actions otherwise permitted by law.  You can delete or deactivate your Bids4cheap account at any time. When you delete your membership, your personal data is removed from our database unless we are required to save the data. As a rule it takes two to three business days until your information is completely removed from all records.

**The Use of Cookies at our Website**  
Bids4cheap uses so-called “cookies”, which are files that are stored on your computer that can be retrieved to assist in customizing your experience with the online service. The information saved supports the functionality of the site, for example by keeping track of your visual preferences or controlling the frequency of “pop-up” windows. You are free to prevent cookies from being saved on your hard drive by adjusting the corresponding settings in your browser. However, we would like to point out that turning off these settings may result in limited functionality.

**Security Measures**  
Your Bids4cheap account and profile and the information contained therein are password protected. Please note that you are not permitted to provide your password to anyone else. Bids4cheap will never ask for your password in e-mails that you receive unexpectedly or that you did not request. Please remember to log out of your account and to close your internet browser window when you leave the Bids4cheap site; this is especially important if you use a PC in public locations. At present, this is the safest way to ensure that no one has access to your personal information. We assume no liability for the abuse of login data and passwords used.  
Further, We treat data as an asset that must be protected. We use lots of security measures to protect your personal information against unauthorized access and disclosure. However, although we work very hard to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

**Protection from Web Crawlers or Spam**  
Bids4cheap assures you that we will use your e-mail address with your express consent only for the purposes stated in the Terms of Use. We will not rent or sell your e-mail address to third parties, and we will prevent your e-mail address from being recorded by “web crawlers” or “web spiders” to the best of our ability. If you believe that your e-mail address has been recorded in this way, please let us know immediately.

**General**  
We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect 10 days after they are initially posted on the site.

 [www.pennyauctionwatch.com/penny-auction-reviews/showproduct.php/cat/2/item/84_www.Bids4Cheap.com](http://www.pennyauctionwatch.com/penny-auction-reviews/showproduct.php/cat/2/item/84_www.Bids4Cheap.com)
